Savings Bank of Manchester Records
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Advertising and Public Relations Records, undated, 1839, 1905-2004
  - Subseries D: Advertisements, 1923-2004
    - Advertisements - Newspaper
      - 2002 (Box 41:, Folder 459)
      - 2003 (Box 41:, Folder 460)
      - 2004 (Box 41:, Folder 461)
    - Advertisements - Programs and Other Publications
      - 1982 (Box 41:, Folder 462)
      - 1994 (Box 41:, Folder 463)
      - 1995 (Box 49:, Folder 464-465)
      - 1996 (Box 49:, Folder 466-467)
      - 1997 (Box 49:, Folder 468-470)
  - Subseries E: Promotional records, ca. 1950s-ca. 2000
    - Columbia Branch Marketing, 1990s (Box 49:, Folder 471)
    - Coventry Branch Marketing, 1990s (Box 49:, Folder 472)
    - Coventry Branch Opening - Large, Inflatable Baseball for Themed Celebration, ca. 1994 (Box 51)
    - Dayville Branch Marketing, 1990s (Box 49:, Folder 473)
    - Discount Coupon Book, 1990-1991 (Box 49:, Folder 474)
    - Discount Coupon Book and Related Records
      - 1991-1992 (Box 49:, Folder 475)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 49:, Folder 476)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 49:, Folder 477)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 49:, Folder 478)
    - Eastford Branch Marketing, 1990s (Box 49:, Folder 479)
    - East Manchester Marketing, ca. 1950s, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 480)
    - East Windsor Branch Marketing, 1985-1991 (Box 49:, Folder 481)
    - Enfield Branch Opening, 1995 (Box 49:, Folder 482-483)
    - "First Baby of the Year" Promotion Records, 1981-1994 (Box 50:, Folder 484)
    - Glastonbury Branch Marketing, 1980s-1990s (Box 50:, Folder 485)
    - GUND Stuffed Animal Inventory, 1990-1993 (Box 50:, Folder 486)
    - "Home Equity Line of Credit" Information, 1988 (Box 50:, Folder 487)
    - "KidsShare" Campaign, 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 488)
    - Mansfield Branch Marketing, 1983-1990s (Box 50:, Folder 489)
    - Memoranda Concerning Various Promotions, 1990 (Box 50:, Folder 490)
    - "NetShop" Program Materials, 2000 (Box 50:, Folder 491)
    - "NetShop" Promotional Display (mini-shopping cart), ca. 2000 (Box 52)
    - North End (Manchester) Branch Marketing, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 492)
    - "On-Line Banking" Software- SBM's Microsoft Money 98, 1998 (Box 52)
    - "Pfd. - Personal Finance Design" Program - Large promotional flip-book, ca. 1980s (Box 53)
    - "SBM Fifty" Account - "Jeopardy"-style Employee Training Records, 1991 (Box 50:, Folder 493-494)
    - S.B.M.- Logo Promotional, "Give-away" Items, undated, ca.1980s-ca.2000 (Box 54-56)
    - SBM 90th Anniversary Materials, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 498)
    - South Windsor Branch Marketing, 1990-2001 (Box 50:, Folder 495)
    - Storrs Branch Marketing, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 496)
    - Tolland Branch Marketing, 1986-1989, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 497)
    - Vernon Branch Marketing, 1988, 1990s (Box 50:, Folder 499)
    - "Welcome" Flipbook - East Windsor Branch, undated (Box 57)
    - "We're Pulling for You!" Materials, undated (Box 50:, Folder 500)
  - Subseries F: Public Relations records, 1980-2002
    - Community Involvement, 1996 (Box 50:, Folder 501)
    - Community Involvement, 1997 (Box 50:, Folder 502)
    - Correspondence with Marketing Firms, 1989 (Box 50:, Folder 503)
    - Correspondence
      - 1993 (Box 50:, Folder 504)
      - 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 505)
      - 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 506)
      - 1996 (Box 50:, Folder 507)
    - Donations, 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 508-510)
    - Donation Requests - Declined, 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 511)
    - Donations - Monetary, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 512-514)
    - Donations of SBM Items, 1995 (Box 58:, Folder 515)
    - Donation Requests - Declined, 1996 (Box 58:, Folder 516)
    - Donations, 1996 (Box 58:, Folder 517)
    - Donations and Sponsorships, 1996 (Box 58:, Folder 518-519)
    - Donations - Items, 1997 (Box 58:, Folder 520)
    - Golf Item Donations, 1997 (Box 58:, Folder 521)
    - News (Press) Releases, 1980-2002 (Box 58:, Folder 527)
    - Plaques of Recognition to SBM from Community Organizations (4), 1990s (Box 61)
  - Subseries G: SBM Historical Items, undated, 1839,1905-2001
    - History of SBM - Master Copy, 1976 (Box 59,62)
    - History-related SBM Items and SBM Ads, 1922-1991 (Box 58:, Folder 522)
    - Historical Objects - SBM Embossers, Charles Dana Paperweight, undated (Box 60)
    - Historical SBM-related Newspaper Notices, 1905 (Box 58:, Folder 523)
    - Historical 'Statements of Condition' File, 1961-1995 (Box 58:, Folder 524)
    - Historical Mural of Manchester- from 923 Main St. Office, undated (Box 59)
    - Large Framed and Matted Full-Page Advertisement from Hartford Daily Courant (Manchester Trust Co. and SBM), 1923 (Box AS)
    - Manchester Tricentennial Committee - SBM, 1976-2001 (Box 58:, Folder 525)
    - Nineteenth-Century Land Deed found in Original Ledger, 1839 (Box 58:, Folder 526)
  - Subseries H: Signage, undated [ca. 1980s-2000s]
    - Small Advertising Posters and Signs (6), undated (Box OS, Folder 62)
    - Large, Framed "Our Community is Our Business" Sign, 1994 (Box AS)
    - Framed Picture of SBM Billboard 'What if it rains tomorrow?' (with car driving through large puddle) (Box AS)
    - Framed and Matted 8x10 Photograph of Old Front Door and Sign at 923 Main St. (Box AS)
    - Outdoor, Vinyl SBM Banners (5), undated (Box OS, Folder 528)
    - Lobby Signs (9), undated (Box OS, Folder 529)
    - Lobby Signs (13), undated (Box OS, Folder 530)
- Series IV: Multimedia materials, undated, bulk 1980s-2000s
  - "Action :30, Canoe :30, and Life on the River :30", 1996 October (Box 63)
  - "Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30, Tugboat :30, Crew #1 :30", undated (Box 63)
  - "Greg - Fish #3", undated (Box 63)
  - "Changes" (Geno) SBM00.03 :30, "NetShop" SBM00.05, Vowel Movement, 2000 October (Box 63)
  - "SBM 1.9.55, 1 x :30, 3 x :10", 1990 January (Box 63)
  - "Tape #4 (With Time Code), 1997 September (Box 63)
  - "Tape #2, SBM, Cam. A, Audio: Ch 1 & 2", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Greg - Fish- Bill", undated (Box 63)
  - "Tape #3, SBM, Cam. A, Audio: Ch 1 & 2" -- written in pencil, "BLANK", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Tape #2, SBM, Cam. B, Audio: Ch 1 & 2", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - 4 spots", undated (Box 63)
  - "Dept. of Defense- Discovering an Untapped Resource - Run time: 15:00 - open caption("our star" Michael), 1999 March (Box 63)
  - "SBM02.03 Rev "When I was a Kid" :30, SBM02.04 Rev "Free Lunch" :30, SBM02.05, Opportunity" :30, SBM02.06 "Teamwork and Success" :30, SBM02.07 "Subway" :15, SBM02.08 "Can't Beat" :10, 2002 October (Box 63)
  - "Tape #1 (Without Time Code), 1997 September (Box 63)
  - "Geno #1 - Ruff Cut, Geno #2 - Ruff Cut", undated (Box 63)
  - "Bank Fees" - w/ note on front- "Chris, Here you are-in living color!" - date 10/22, undated (Box 63)
  - "Life on the River"- Tape #2 and 2A, Window Dub, 1996 August (Box 63)
  - "Life on the River"- Tape #1, Window Dub, 1996 August (Box 63)
  - "Connecticut Bancshares, Welcome Ceremony" - produced by NASDAQ, 2001 March (Box 63)
  - "Action :30, Canoe :30, and Life on the River :30", 1996 October (Box 63)
  - no label, except Donna Cammeyer business card (P.R./Advertising for SBM), undated (Box 63)
  - "Geno-Big is Better, :30" "Geno-Big Little, :30" "Acquisition, :10"-Vowel Movement, 2001 August (Box 63)
  - "Tape #1, SBM, Audio: Ch. 1 and 2, Cam. B", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Tape #3, SBM, Cam. B, Audio: Ch. 1 and 2" - also says in pencil "BLANK", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Fishing, :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30, Tugboat :30, Crew #1-Generic - Ch. 1 & 2, Stereo Mix - SUBMASTER, undated (Box 63)
  - "RiverFest '95 - 11:00 HR.T.C.", 1995 (Box 63)
  - "Camera 1, Tape 1, Rowing Close-ups", undated (Box 63)
  - "Tape #1, SBM, Audio: Ch. 1 and 2, Cam. A", 2000 May (Box 63)
  - "Who Wants to Be A Millionaire" starring Nancy Bussiere - Recorded 'live' at Adams Mill -- On 3/14/00 Checking Account Campaign Kickoff, 2000 March (Box 63)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester, 1. Action, 2. Riverlife, 3. Canoe", undated (Box 63)
  - "SBM Radio - 1. Geno "Goals" :60, 2. Geno "Community" :60, undated (Box 63)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - (2) :60 spots-1. Free Lunch, 2. When I Was A Kid", 2002 August (Box 63)
  - PowerPoint presentation to train employees in Microsoft Outlook 98, 1998 (Box 63)
  - "Jeff - fish - #3", n.d (Box 64)
  - "1.Headbangers :30, 2. Unbelievable :30", undated (Box 64)
  - "Cross-Selling Banking Services" produced by Bureau of Business Practices, 1986 (Box 64)
  - "INVEST - Investment Services for America - Length 14:05", undated (Box 64)
  - "Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30; w/ Titles, Ch. 1 and 2 Stereo Mix", 1996 (Box 64)
  - "Fox 61 News @ Ten - Mike Robinson, Jim Brochu", 1998 February (Box 64)
  - "Action :30, Canoe :30, Life on the River :30, Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2, :30, Tugboat, :30, Crew #1 :30", undated (Box 64)
  - Rockville Area Chamber of Commerce - "A Good Place to Grow" - 12:30 minutes, 1990 (Box 64)
  - "Headbangers :30, Unbelievable :30", undated (Box 64)
  - "Fishing, River, Crew#2, Tugboat, Crew#1 - 5 spots @ :30 each, Stereo Mix, Ch. 1 & 2", undated (Box 64)
  - "Tug Boat from Boat", undated (Box 64)
  - "Effects", 1996 October (Box 64)
  - "3 WFSB-TV - Savings Bank of Manchester :30", undated (Box 64)
  - "1. Exploding the Sales Myth, 2. Customer Connection, 3. Total Teller, 4. We're Close, 5. Harland Portrait, 6. Missed Opportunities, 7. Mapping the Future, 8. Mapping the Future #2, 9. High Tech/High Touch, undated (Box 64)
  - "Bank Fees", undated (Box 64)
  - "SBM 1.9.55 - 1 x :30, 3 x :10" - VideoCraft, 1990 January (Box 64)
  - "Senior Advantage" - FISI Video Network, 1984 (Box 64)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - 1. Headbangers :30, 2. Unbelievable, :30", undated (Box 64)
  - "Big Kiss, Aerobics, Stock Market, Sofa, Office Friend", 1987 February (Box 64)
  - "John Fannon - 617-877-2604, Bach Piece - SBM", undated (Box 64)
  - "Aircheck" - WTIC 1080, 1989 April (Box 64)
  - "Aircheck" - WTIC 1080, 1989 April (Box 64)
  - "Aircheck" - WTIC 1080, 1989 April (Box 64)
  - "Sid" -- :45 Radio, 1990 March (Box 64)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester/2", undated (Box 64)
  - "1. Baby 2. Divorce 3. Car Pool 4. Women 5. Late 6. Woof :60 's", undated (Box 64)
  - "WINF 1230, 'Yankee Wrap-up Show'", undated (Box 64)
  - WINF - "IAN Bland - SBM Mobile Bank-- Focus on WINF", undated (Box 64)
  - "1. Express Bank A :10, 2. Express Bank B :10, 3. Express Bank :30", undated (Box 64)
  - "Cindy :60, Ray :60, SBM / 0.67", 1991 March (Box 64)
  - "SBA-CONN, Shirley Martin Campaign", undated (Box 64)
  - "Smile, Columbia!", undated (Box 64)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester, Bill :60 / Alice :60", 1991 March (Box 64)
  - "Swat Team :60 sec", undated (Box 64)
  - "Swat Team" :60, Produced by: Keiler & Company, 1993 September (Box 64)
  - "1. Pet Store :60" Produced by: Joy Radio for Keiler, 1994 April (Box 64)
  - "Yankee Wrap-up", undated (Box 64)
  - "(3) :60 Savings Bank of Manchester, Demo Spots", 1987 November (Box 64)
  - "WHCN Express Bank - news story", undated (Box 64)
  - "1. Big Kiss, 2. Aerobics, 3. Stock Market, 4. Sofa, 5. Office Friend", 1987 February (Box 64)
  - "1. Baby, 2. Divorcee, 3. Car Pool, 4. Woman Talk, 5. Woof, 6. Bald/Late", undated (Box 64)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - Adams, Rickard, Mason - 7 spots", 1986 February (Box 64)
  - "Smile Columbia!", undated (Box 64)
  - "Smile Columbia!", undated (Box 64)
  - "Smile Columbia!", undated (Box 64)
  - "1. Late Starters :60 (Bald Version)", undated (Box 64)
  - "SBM - (3) :60 Radios", 1995 February (Box 64)
  - "(3) :60 Radio Spots - FINAL", 1988 January (Box 64)
  - "BOSTON 1, CLEVELAND 0 - 10/6/48 Game 1, World Series - Jim Britt and Mel Allen, 1992 (Box 64)
  - "SBM Over 50, 'Bill' :60, 'Alice' :60 --- SBM 1.1.04, 1991 March (Box 64)
  - "(3) :60 Radio 1) East of the River, 2) Hello, 3) Checking Club, 1989 March (Box 64)
  - "Swat Team" :60R --Produced by Keiler & Company, 1993 September (Box 64)
  - "SBM Jingle", undated (Box 64)
  - 1) Geno "Teamwork" :30, 2) Geno "Community" :30, 3) "River" :30, 4) "Crew" :30, 5) "Crew 2" :30, 6) "On-Line Banking" :30, 1999 November (Box 65)
  - Tape #4 (Without Time Code), 1997 September (Box 65)
  - Tape #5 (Without Time Code), 1997 September (Box 65)
  - "Geno" Tape 3 (With Time Code), 1999 August (Box 65)
  - "Geno" Tape 2 with time code, 1999 August (Box 65)
  - SBM - PC Onine, "Raymond in Canoe," Tape #1 of 1, 1998 June (Box 65)
  - Tape #2 - SBM - Audio: Ch.1 & 2 boom, 2001 April (Box 65)
  - # 2 Rigatta, Camera # 2, 1998 (Box 65)
  - "Life on the River" Tape # 1, 1996 August (Box 65)
  - # 1 Rigatta, 1998 (Box 65)
  - Tape #1, Brant, TVG, etc., 1998 (Box 65)
  - Sign - Wethersfield, undated (Box 65)
  - SBM boat yard, Tape # 2, 1998 October (Box 65)
  - Life on the River, Tape # 2, 1996 August (Box 65)
  - #4 Rigatta, 1998 (Box 65)
  - SBM Jeff's cam, SBM #1 time code - Grace and Raymond - canoe (family on bicycle), undated (Box 65)
  - SBM "On-line Banking" :30 - MASTER, 1998 October (Box 65)
  - "Horse on river, from boat (1 min)", undated (Box 65)
  - "Life on the River, crowds and banners", 1996 July (Box 65)
  - "Tug/Water/ Greg", undated (Box 65)
  - "Greg's cam #2 time code, bike path from shore", undated (Box 65)
  - Jeff - fish - Bill, undated (Box 65)
  - Tape #1, SBM, Audio: Ch. 1 & 2 boom, 2001 April (Box 65)
  - Ski jump competition, undated (Box 65)
  - #3 Rigatta, 1998 (Box 65)
  - SBM - boat yard - Tape #1, 1998 October (Box 65)
  - Tape 2 - SBM - 6pm, 1996 February (Box 65)
  - 1) Action :30, 2) Canoe :30, 3) Life on the River :30, 1996 October (Box 65)
  - Geno/ scoring 2 - rough, 2001 May (Box 65)
  - Geno/ ten, 2001 May (Box 65)
  - Tape 1 - SBM - 4PM, 1996 February (Box 65)
  - SBM - Rough Cut #1, undated (Box 65)
  - Rough cut - boat yard :30, "On-line Banking", undated (Box 65)
  - Fishing, River, Crew #2, Tugboat, Crew #1 -- :30 spots, Ch. 1 and 2 Stereo Mix, undated (Box 65)
  - Geno/ scoring, 2001 May (Box 65)
  - Action :30, Canoe :30, Life on the River :30, 1996 October (Box 65)
  - Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30, Tugboat :30, Crew #1 :30-Ch. 1 and 2 Stereo Mix -- EDIT MASTER - internet address added 10/31/96 - old voice, 1996 October (Box 65)
  - SBM Crew #1, RT: :30 - EDIT MASTER - Ch. 1 & 2 Stereo Mix - Produced by "Freelance Tomatoes/Holly Beckett", 1995 November (Box 65)
  - Savings Bank of Manchester - 3 spots, 1996 October (Box 66)
  - Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30, Tugboat :30, Crew #1 :30, undated (Box 66)
  - Tape #1 (with Time Code) - "Rowing", 1997 September (Box 66)
  - Geno - "Big is Better" :30, Geno-"Big Little" :30, Acquisition :10, Vowel Move., 2001 October (Box 66)
  - Tape #3 (With Time Code) - also paper in case reading "single scull birds", 1997 September (Box 66)
  - Tape #2 (With Time Code) - written "Long Lens Rowing", 1997 September (Box 66)
  - Action :30, Canoe :30, Life on the River :30, Fishing :30, River :30, Crew #2 :30,Tugboat :30, Crew #1 :30 - written arrows point to # 3 and # 5, undated (Box 66)
  - Consumer Group #3, 2/17/00, 5:00 pm, 2000 February (Box 66)
  - "@ 6:00 PM", 2000 February (Box 66)
  - Consumer Group # 1, 4:00 PM, 2000 February (Box 66)
  - "7:00 PM", 2000 February (Box 66)
  - "SBM GUITAR MUSIC-- Studio: Holly Becket, Client: SBM, Program: 1.Guitar Music :60 2. Guitar Music :30, Engineer: Andy", 1998 December (Box 66)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester -- :30 TV Music - 44.1 Khz", undated (Box 66)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - Raws and Mixes" -- 1-19 = V.O. Raws, 20= SBM Canoe Mix, 21= SBM Canoe V.O., 22= SBM River Mix, 23= SBM River V.O., 24=Music Only. 44.1K., undated (Box 66)
  - "Savings Bank of Manchester - (3) :30 Spot Mixes" -- 1) SBM "River Action" :30, 2) SBM "Canoe" :30, 3) SBM "Life on the River" :30. At 48K, undated (Box 66)
  - Enfield Opening - Ken Burns, "The Shakers: Hands to Work, Hearts to God", 1985 (Box 66)
  - Enfield Opening - "Shaker Songs: Come to Zion" - Hancock Shaker Village, 1993 (Box 66)
  - Enfield Opening - "Simple Gifts: Instrumental Arrangements of Shaker Melodies" by William Coulter and Barry Phillips, 1990 (Box 66)
  - "L'Histoire Du Soldat," Robert J. Lurtsema - narrator, to be performed by Hop River Chamber Players, July 9-13, 1995. From file P.R - Donations - 1995, 1995 July (Box 66)
- Series V: Photographs, undated, ca. 1960s-2000s
  - Expandable file folder of B&W employee portraits, arranged alphabetically (last pocket contains Misc. photos, including Bank historical photos, undated, [Bulk ca. 1990s] (Box 67)
  - Folder of photos separated from other parts of collection, undated (Box 67)
  - Folder of photos from SBM golf outings, 1994-1995 (Box 67)
  - Gold box of photographs, many B&W, mostly "photo-op" and various bank building photos, ca. 1960s-1990s (Box 67)
  - Binder of Photographs from SBM Functions, 1995-1998 (Box 68)
  - Envelope of photos - SBM softball, picnic, etc., 1999 (Box 68)
  - Envelope of photos - KidsBank Halloween Party, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Slides of SBM flip chart for "Pfd." program, 1979 January (Box 68)
  - Matted collection of (6) photos, including cake from 80th SBM Anniversary, 1985 (Box 68)
  - Matted collection of (4) photos, ca. 1980s (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Savings Bank side when Trust Co. and Savings side were in 1st floor of bank lobby", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Richard P. Meduski, Pres."- flying a kite, undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "L to R- Roger Somerville, Kathleen Williams, Charles Pike, Eugene Olsen, Douglas Anderson", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Duplicate" of employees standing in lobby, ca. 1973 (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Manchester Office" - store fronts, undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Larry Gaucher, Debbie Casanant, Joyce Trainer, Rick, ?, Nancy Bussiere, Liz Ramsey", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Donna Cammeyer and customer" - flying a kite, undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Mary Michand, Joan Sieverts, Mary Anderson -- all branch managers later", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Richard P. Meduski, Pres.", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "Harry Gaucher - VP - MTG, Charles L. Pike - EVP", undated (Box 68)
  - Matted photo - "M.O.D.I" - [Manchester Office Drive-In?], undated (Box 68)